{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731545449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731545448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731548725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731548725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" itakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUWA"," userResponse":" ITAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731551742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731551742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731555115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731555115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731557947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731557947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731561761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731561760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731564958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731564958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" SAWASAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731568419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731568419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731571833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731571833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731575126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731575125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731578814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731578813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731578900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731578899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731586469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731586469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" dffb8857-3c2a-4d59-8a17-645dd3449c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731627065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731627065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_jivu-kuwa-wale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731636605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731636605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_umwa_amua-choo-umwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" umwa"," userResponse":" choo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731646523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731646523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_umwa_amua-choo-umwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" umwa"," userResponse":" umwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731656389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731656388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_pesa-kwao-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731666985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731666985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kuwa-giza-humu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731679602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731679602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwa_tani-ziwa-kuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731690335","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731690335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_huwa-waje-tele"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731705336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731705336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dawa_debe-yule-dawa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dawa"," userResponse":" dawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731739721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731739721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kitu-kuwa-yule"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731749650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731749650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kitu-kuwa-yule"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731776392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731776392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_huwa-lisa-miye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731787745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731787744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpwa_zote-kifo-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpwa"," userResponse":" mpwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731793504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731793503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mpwa_zote-kifo-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731802294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731802294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" bbb39440-58f5-46e1-8c51-ea360006a202"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mpwa_zote-kifo-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731812210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731812209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 398a8f06-7397-4164-a745-0e33e1ce07f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731822249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731822249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 398a8f06-7397-4164-a745-0e33e1ce07f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731823721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731823721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 398a8f06-7397-4164-a745-0e33e1ce07f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731823811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731823810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 398a8f06-7397-4164-a745-0e33e1ce07f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731840616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731840616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 398a8f06-7397-4164-a745-0e33e1ce07f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731853990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731853990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731859077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731859077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731860613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731860613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731864159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731864159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731865709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731865709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731870423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731870423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731871985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731871985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731879732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731879732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731879836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731879836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731885176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731885175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" 52251fcf-2838-43b7-86d9-c7fd3d3af1b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731898937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731898936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_waua-huwa-sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731908412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731908412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_umwa_umwa-adie-zako"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" umwa"," userResponse":" umwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549731992660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549731992659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miwa_nini-lake-miwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miwa"," userResponse":" miwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732009390","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732009390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwa_omba-hapo-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732019479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732019479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpwa_lina-wiki-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpwa"," userResponse":" mpwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732034727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732034727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_juma-gogo-hewa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" gogo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732043827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732043826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_juma-gogo-hewa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" hewa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732054472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732054472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_hizi-hewa-wote"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" hewa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732063996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732063996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_nije-kuwa-geni"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732073750","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732073750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_boga-hewa-taji"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" hewa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732109358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732109358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sawa_lulu-sawa-bado"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sawa"," userResponse":" sawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732115093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732115093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" f79bee19-910e-417f-98f6-a1784ed7ac7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_sawa_lulu-sawa-bado"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732150859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732150859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_boga-hewa-taji"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" hewa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732176663","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732176663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_hizi-hewa-wote"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" hewa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732211147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732211146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sawa_lulu-sawa-bado"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sawa"," userResponse":" sawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732236029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732236029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_umwa_umwa-adie-zako"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" umwa"," userResponse":" umwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732247378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732247378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_nije-kuwa-geni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" nije"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732292326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732292326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_nije-kuwa-geni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732301489","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732301489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miwa_nini-lake-miwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miwa"," userResponse":" miwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732304179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732304179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_195850"," gameId":" ba8320f7-87de-4e69-9b7b-e1cca344cdab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_miwa_nini-lake-miwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}